Good morning!
Rise and shine!
This is Morioh Radio.
Kai Harada, here,
keeping you company this A.M
And what a morning it is!
Today's gonna be a beauty,
and I have just what
the doctor ordered
All you have to do is
sit back and enjoy
Oh, there it is.
The reception usually clears up
once you're past the tower.
First time in Morioh, sir?
Yeah.
Anything I should know?
Morioh? Hmm…
Ah!
The miso-marinated beef
tongue is good.
Anything unusual?
Strange incidents?
Sorry, young man…
Afraid I can't help you there.
Um, would you kindly
remind me of our destination?
Yes, in front of the station.
No problem.
Good grief…
This'd better not be what I think it is.
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
I remember it was April, 1999.
EPISODE 1
JOTARO KUJO! MEETS JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA
It was my first day of high school,
And I was about to make
two very bizarre friends.
So today I become a high schooler.
Wonder what the other kids'll be like…
If you care to know,
my name's Koichi Hirose.
Though, I guess,
it's not that big a deal.
Anyway, I was walking to class,
nervous as can be, and then…
Oh! Wha—?
I could've sworn I just…
All my stuff…
Sorry, I wasn't paying attention.
He's giant!
He must be
over 190 centimeters tall!
Maybe you can help me.
Do you know of a family
by the name of Higashikata?
Higashikata? Well…
Then how bout this address?
Jozenji 1-6.
Jotaro Kujo…
You can get to Jozenji
by taking the #3 bus.
It won't be long before
one comes around.
Thanks.
I first met him, Jotaro Kujo.
Turns out he's twenty eight
and a marine explorer.
Academics apparently know him
for his bio research.
There's something fierce
but also intellectual about him…
Wow..
Hey! You another freshman?
What, no introduction?
S-Sir!
I'm freshman Koichi Hirose.
Good day, sir!
All right. That's more like it.
Y-Yikes!
Don't worry.
Those guys'll get on a different bus.
The hell you doing, dick face?!
Who do you think you are?
What am I doing? Well…
Seems this turtle here just
woke up from his hibernation.
Turtles give me the willies.
I can barely touch 'em.
So I thought I might conquer
my fears, kinda…
I don't give a shit!
Get up, dumb-ass!
Well, well…
Pretty tall for a pathetic freshman.
But… if you wanna dress
like a pompous prick…
you gotta pay your respects
to us first!
Um, reptiles kinda
give me the heebie-jeebies.
They're so creepy…
What are you smirking at?
Forgive me.
I didn't know, sir.
I've put a lot of guys in the ho spit a I
whose last words were exactly that.
You wanna end up
like this turtle?! Huh?!
He's sick…
I'll have mercy on you this time.
You can leave your jacket
and pants here with us.
And your cash, too!
Right, I'm very sorry, sir.
Dress like that,
and you're asking for trouble.
What pisses me off…
is how he can just sit back and watch
them pulverize that turtle.
Hey, pussy!
Why don't you tell us your name?
Of course.
Class 1 -B.
Josuke Higashikata.
What?
Josuke Higashikata?
"Jo" and "Jo," eh?
Josuke, huh?
"JoJo" is gonna be
your name from now on!
Oh…
Thank you very much.
So take off that jacket already!
The freak in bus is here!
Hurry it up,
or I'll chop that fugly cowlick straight off!
What's the matter? Hurry up!
Excuse me, sir…
What'd you just say
about my hair?
What? A Stand?!
My nose… My teeth!
Talk shit about my hair,
and feel pain
like you've never felt!
So my hair looks like
a freak in toupee, huh?
Huh?! No one said…
I know what I heard, dammit!
What the?
That punk just went flying.
There's no doubt.
I saw a Stand just now
Huh? That turtle's cuts are…
What the hell?
Your nose and teeth
are healing themselves!
Hey, he's all better!
But his face is all weird now!
It's changed!
Huh?
No! What happened
to my face? Hey!
Thanks to you,
I had to go and touch something
I didn't really want to touch.
How're you gonna
make it up to me now, huh?!
Wait! My nose!
What happened to it? Huh?
Good grief.
This guy…
Gah! Holy shit!
Oh, that turtle again.
So I was right.
The turtle's healed
Josuke Higashikata…
Born: 1983
Mother's name: Tomoko
She was twenty-one,
attending university in Tokyo.
You've called this town home
your entire life.
Then, in 1987,
when you were four,
you came down
with a mysterious fever.
For fifty days,
you were at death's door.
Your father's name is…
Good grief
How'd I get stuck in
the middle of this?
Your father's name is
Joseph Joestar.
He's seventy-eight.
And founder of Joestar Realty.
The Joseph Joestar?
He's that American real estate mogul.
Don't worry, he's fine.
When I was looking into how
to divide his properties,
I learned he had a son,
that would be you, living in Japan.
Even the old man had no idea.
Piece of shit…
Bastard said his wife
was his one and only.
Then I find you, the son he fathered
when he had his affair
at the ripe old age of sixty-two.
Sorry, guess
I shouldn't have said that.
I'm Jotaro Kujo.
I guess, technically,
I'm your nephew.
Weird, huh?
Nephew?
Um, it's a pleasure.
Come on, let's talk.
So, eventually, a third of the
old man's inheritance will go to you.
That's the message
I've come to pass on.
The old man's affair
has turned
the Joestar family
upside down.
Upside down?
Yeah… My grandma, Suzie Q,
is the angriest she's ever been
in their 61 years of marriage.
Forgive me!
This is all my fault!
Hey. Wait a second.
Why are you apologizing?
Well, I'd hate to be the cause
of the family falling apart.
My mother always said
she was deeply in love.
That's enough for me.
Could you tell, uh, my dad, or…
Mr. Joestar,
he doesn't have to
concern himself with us?
Thank you.
What's with this kid?
I came here ready to be decked
on behalf of the old man,
and instead he's apologizing?
Hey, it's Josuke!
So it is!
Josuke!
– How are you?
– What a coincidence!
Come with me to class?
Your hair looks as handsome as ever.
Looking good!
You're different from the other guys.
Um… We're actually in the middle of
an important chat…
Ah, come on!
If you don't hurry up,
you're gonna be late.
You can talk later.
Hey, Josuke.
We're not done talking.
Get 'em out of here.
Who the hell is this guy?
Hey, you can waste your time
talking about his hair later.
He's done it now.
Not his hair!
You bastard…
What'd you say
about my hair?!
This isn't good.
Don't blame me!
Josuke can't stand it when
someone disses his hair.
It's just what happened before!
Hold it, Josuke.
That wasn't meant to…
Dammit! Here it comes!
Josuke!
He's bleeding!
See it, Josuke?
This is a Stand.
A physical manifestation
of the soul.
Joseph Joestar has one, too.
Only a Stand user
can see another Stand.
It pisses me off when someone
bad-mouths my pride and joy.
It really pisses me off!
So this is Josuke's Stand!
His power…
Your chest's wide open!
Bastard!
What?!
Huh?
When did that-
What's going on?
Bastard, when did y–
Josuke!
– No!
–Josuke!
Shut the hell up!
That bitching irritates me to all hell!
Get lost!
Fine…
Guess they know each other.
He's kinda scary.
And hot…
I don't understand..
I don't understand any of it!
This is all too weird!
It's been a while…
Ten years, actually
I managed to stop time
for half a second only
If I hadn't stopped time…
I doubt we would've been killed,
but one of us
would've been injured bad
Here, Josuke.
Ah, uh… No. It's okay.
All right.
There's another
reason I came to see you.
It's in this picture.
Something evil is
lurking in this town.
A catastrophic danger is
fast approaching
When the old man uses his
psychic photography
to get a picture of you,
this is the result.
We don't know why…
But he's likely a Stand user.
This is all new to you, I know,
but I wanted
to show you the picture.
Be careful.
Koichi…
If you catch sight of him,
stay far away.
Involving the police won't help.
You have to run.
Josuke…
Keep your cool
and stay out of it.
Or, like a moment ago,
you'll be sorry you did.
Agh! High school orientation!
Ack! It's already time!
Shit…
My mom's gonna kill me
if I show up late the first day!
Hey, I'll listen to everything
you've got to say after school.
Hey, Koichi, right? Let's go!
Huh?
Come on!
Okay!
This is Josuke Higashikata,
the other weird friend I made.
One moment he's shy
and unassuming,
the next he's gone
completely mental.
His family situation is complicated
And we only just met…
Josuke Higashikata…
He's anything but normal.
And his Stand..
This hat…
It's back together but…
His Stand destroys objects
then rearranges their structure.
If he'd gotten
my face or my skull…
Talk about gruesome.
But as an ally, he could make
a more than capable fighter.
Excluding that bizarre personality
of his, anyway
I hope this doesn't involve Josuke.
JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA
SHINING DIAMOND
Hey, good lookin'!
Where ya headed?
Let me give you a ride.
Hey, no need to be shy!
C'mon! C'mon!
Ooh, v-very pretty!
So you'll go wherever I want?
You bet!
I'll go anywhere you want me to!
Then how bout a one-way trip to hell!
Huh?
Hey, son, you all right?
Officer!
Go catch that crazy bitch!
That's assault! Assault!
Nope, no can do.
What?!
Well, she's my daughter.
Huh?
Well, let's see.
You caused a public nuisance,
and referred to my daughter
as a crazy bitch.
I'll let you go this time.
Let's be a bit more
careful next time, shall we?
Madame Murakami,
are you all right?
Here, I'll carry your bag.
Hey, Tomoko!
Dad.
Heading home?
Yep.
I'll keep you company.
I'm done for the day.
How's Josuke?
Today was orientation, right?
He'd better not be
up to any trouble.
Hmph. Who knows?
That moron may look innocent,
but he can lose it at the drop of a hat.
I wonder
where he gets that from.
Hey, easy there…
But…
Deep down,
he's a genuine, good kid.
I'm not worried.
That's the spirit.
Now tonight we can celebrate.
That was my plan.
I doubt he'll come
straight home, though.
He likes his detours.
That he does.
Hey, I wanna stop by Kameyu.
Huh? I just bought you an
expensive bag!
I want to look at clothes today!
Watch it, dumb-ass!
Watch where
you're walking, moron.
That guy weirds me out.
He slams into someone
and can't so much as apologize?
Forget it. Let's go.
I know. You just wanna go to
Kameyu, right?
Huh?
Anjuro Katagiri, a.k.a. Angelo.
Born in Morioh, 1964.
IQ: 160.
He was sent to juvie
for robbery and rape
when he was just twelve years old.
That was just the beginning.
He became known as
the most violent,
shocking criminal to have
ever walked Japanese soil.
He spent most of his youth in jail,
twenty years by the time
he'd turned thirty-four.
His final crime was so sinister,
it'd make a sewer rat puke.
He was eventually arrested,
and was sentenced to…
death.
But the execution didn't kill him.
Angelo escaped shortly after.
He likely became a Stand
user right before his execution.
I have no idea why,
but he's hiding in the shadows
of this quiet town…
somewhere.
Oh, Koichi, heading home?
Oh… Yeah.
So we're in the same class.
Yeah… What a coincidence.
Well, see ya tomorrow.
Um… Hey! J-Josuke!
Huh?
So you want to hear what
that Jotaro guy has to say?
I can't stop thinking about it.
It's all happening in our own backyard.
That's admirable.
But I think I'll pass.
Why?
I was sorta curious,
but after thinking it through,
I figured it'd be best to
keep clear of this
whole lovechild fiasco.
Why?
Well, I mean…
Things are just fine
the way they are now.
I see…
What's that?
Some kind of accident?
Wanna check it out?
Sure.
What? Are they filming a drama?
It's unsafe, get back.
Get back!
What a commotion!
A man robbing that
convenience store
has taken the female employee
hostage inside.
Huh?
Look! He's coming out!
Freeze!
Put down the knife!
– Let the girl go!
– Shut up! Move back!
Th-That lady has
rung me up before!
I can see it in his eyes.
If he loses it, he'll kill her for sure.
All you fools, outta the way!
I'm getting into the car!
This isn't good, Josuke!
Get back! Back!
– R-Right, sorry. Let us step back.
– You, with the dumb-ass hair!
I told you to get away from the car!
I'll kill you!
I have…
a bad feeling about this.
I knew it!
Oh no! Here it comes!
Right now? Right here?
And Mr. Jotaro warned him!
Who's that?
H-Hey! Stop!
The hell you just say?
Wh-Who the hell are you?
Get the hell away from me!
I'll gut her right here, I swear!
Move away, you fool!
If he snaps, you're done for!
You bastards stay back, too!
God dammit!
That's fucking it!
I'm gonna do it!
I'm gonna slaughter this bitch!
Is that so?
H-He's got a hole in his body!
Did I piss you off?
You should know,
that's my line!
Huh? I-I'm totally fine!
She's back to normal.
It's happening again!
M-My knife! It's inside my body!
H-How the…?!
You'd better get a surgeon to take
that out… in the prison hospital.
S-Seize him!
What's going on?
Josuke!
Hey, Koichi.
Are you okay?!
That was…
What the…
What the hell's happening?
Well, what a surprise!
We have another Stand user!
And I was having so much fun
using that louse for my armed robbery…
Then you had to get in my way!
He's the guy from the picture!
I'll be keeping an eye on you.
Wherever you are.
Whatever you do.
What'd you say, dirt bag?!
Josuke!
You idiot! Get him!
– The hell was all that?!
– W-Wait a sec…
Mr. Jotaro was telling the truth.
Something is in this town…
I can feel it.
Something bizarre.
Something here in Morioh…
Something terrible!
Hey, Josuke! Get the phone!
Josuke!
Answer the damn phone!
Yeah, yeah. I'm getting it…
Hello…
It's Jotaro.
Oh, hi.
Our conversation yesterday
was too brief
We need to talk about
the guy hiding in this town.
Um, well, I wanted to
talk about that.
Mr. Jotaro, where are you?
The Morioh Grand Hotel.
What's up?
Since you mention it…
Dammit, freak in pisses me off.
Where the hell did I put the shovel?
Little brat…
He's got the perfect little family.
Not to mention
a hot, young mom…
Lucky bastard…
Josuke Higashikata,
better not get too cocky.
Cause I'm gonna
stomp on your soul
and your precious
little life.
EPISODE 2
JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA! MEETS ANGELO